[Music]
welcome back here watching from the
stand on ET now
well well buying a life insurance policy
will soon be much easier on your pocket
competition is pushing insurers to make
their products Innovative and much more
affordable in fact Bera sunlife
insurance for example is planning to
launch a new term insurance plan which
will be the cheapest yet for those with
Healthy Lifestyles May shety of the
economic Times now joins us on the phone
line may could you run us through the
details of this particular policy that
basan life is looking to
sell uh this policy is a standard term
insurance policy but the difference here
is that instead of uh uh uh offering
standard rates for the best customers
they have decided to have a have a
discount on the standard rates so if you
are if you if the policy holders got a
uh healthier than average Lifestyle then
he can aail of discounts uh this is not
this is not something that's quite new
internationally because there are
policies where uh customers get
discounts for uh member for being
members of uh for having a gym
membership or uh having a
other things that will improve their uh
lifestyle right right May thanks very
much for those details so that could be
a life insurance policy that you might
be looking to buy but before we go
across to hmon Mishra of Standard
Chartered bank to get a sense of how the
what the outlook for the currency in
bond markets is uh let's take a quick
look at where the equity markets are at
now uh if we could just pull those uh
the set of Graphics
up from F myself and the rest of the
team that put together from the stands
thanks very much for watching us up next
is inside Ed stay with us